<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CityGoer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_public_transit">publicTransitActivity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--yelp-->
    <string name="client_id">hVaxvMhxrHGiseUxsqRqsg</string>
    <string name="client_secret">yQYeAE2aMUgSaolBZza0YNYafjAJkZVB4pQ0wL1JGwWP4cIMEmPWc45kADWuIJtz</string>
    <string name="access_token">2sBNK7TrgKWs9_n6gYkScn0JzIgoXOZgzAy8UsUWBzUiV7YUM1S-bv4VUXrDxrbUVfzxpo33Z5f6OfAv23m5foKP7gILNzmA1KUlROByxT81PSYx7tEVUL6dJub0WHYx
    </string>

    <string name="consumerKey">UJ1a_felexDlK-XN35ynwA</string>
    <string name="consumerSecret">TLbRGlmBek8j8ZcnlR8X97ug48Q</string>
    <string name="token">tp8H0AAccrrzAcDT_YMKm8ZTUlD8IlbZ</string>
    <string name="tokenSecret">ZhFj842hkZpSPt2lijHPLFTgxNE</string>

    <string name="forbiddenCity_info">The shape of the Forbidden City is a rectangle. It stretches
        3,153 feet from the north to the south and 2470 feet from west to east. \n It consists of
        980 buildings with 8,886 rooms. The construction of this city took 14 years and over a
        million workers. The main resource to construct the building was whole logs.</string>
    <string name="greatWall_info">The Great Wall of China is a series of fortifications. The Great
        Wall is 5,500.3 miles long or 8,858.8 kilometers.
        \nIt is mainly made up of bricks, wood, rammed earth, and stone. </string>
    <string name="mingTomb_info"> The Ming tombs are a collection of mausoleums built by the
        emperors of the Ming dynasty of China. The tomb of the first Ming emperor is located near his
        capital Nanjing. However, the majority of the Ming tombs are located in a cluster near
        Beijing and collectively known as the Thirteen Tombs of the Ming Dynasty. \n
    The siting of the Ming dynasty imperial tombs was carefully chosen according to Feng Shui
        (geomancy) principles. According to these, bad spirits and evil winds descending from
        the North must be deflected. The area is 40 kilometers and is completely enclosed by
        mountains in a valley full of dark earth and tranquil water.</string>
    <string name="templeofHeaven_info">The temple of Heaven is for religious purposes. These buildings
        are in the southeastern part of Beijin. They are visited by the emperors of the Ming and
        Qing dynasties for yearly ceremonies for prayer to the heavens for good harvest of crops.
        \n The temple complex was constructed from 1406 to 1420 during the reign of the Yongle Emperor,
        who was also responsible for the construction of the Forbidden City in Beijing.
        The Temple grounds cover 2.73 km² of parkland and comprises three main groups of constructions,
        all built according to strict philosophical requirements.</string>
    <string name="summerPalace_info">The Summer Palace sits on Longevity Hill and the hill is about
        60 meters or 200 feet in height.The front hill is rich with splendid halls and pavilions, while
        the back hill, in sharp contrast, is quiet with natural beauty. The central Kunming Lake, covering
        2.2 square kilometres (540 acres), was entirely man-made and the excavated soil was used to build
        Longevity Hill. </string>

</resources>
